ncrcities.com 2016-11-24

# Privacy Policy | NCRCITIES.COM

**Information collection and Use**

When you register on the NCRCities.com , you may have to provide your personal or business information.

**Personal Data**

NCRCities.com collects personal data from you when you add business contents on NCRCities.com, We provide you with the support and tools required to maintain and modify your directory listings; and to contact you about specials and new products.

NCRCities.com collects personally identifiable data from you when you request corrections to, or deletions of, directory listings in order to process your request.

You can change or correct information about yourself and your account by contacting us at the email address: info@NCRCities.com.

**Vistors Data** :

 In an effort to provide maximum benefit to you we collect information, not about you personally, but about your visit. We are constantly monitoring information in order to produce aggregate reports for internal use and for use by third parties, including advertisers. This information provides us with valuable feedback we can use to improve our site and services. For example, we can inform advertisers how many people saw or clicked on an ad and additionally, how many people saw or clicked on ads in different portions of our service. Where available, we may offer information about aggregate viewer characteristics. We do not include personally identifiable information about you or your online usage patterns.

NCRCities.com collects information about your site usage through the use of cookies and through our server log files, including IP Addresses. NCRCities.com does not link IP Addresses to any personally identifiable information.

Cookies allow us to customize portions of our content according to your preferences. Cookies also allow us to target our advertisements and limit the number of times you see an advertisement on our site. However, cookies tell us nothing about you personally unless you specifically give us additional information. The NCRCities.com web site is viewable even if you disable the cookie function.

Some of the banner and display ads on our site are provided by third party ad servers. These ads may contain cookies. Information collected through cookies associated with third party ads are collected by the third party and we do not always have access to this information. We use reputable third parties to serve some or all of the advertisements that are placed within our site.

**Information Sharing** :

NCRCities.com does not sell any personally identifiable information to any telemarketing, direct marketing or commercial mass e-mail companies, agents or representatives.

NCRCities.com will send personally identifiable information to other companies or people when:

NCRCities.com needs to share the information to provide a product or service you requested;

NCRCities.com has a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order or other legal process;

NCRCities.com finds that your actions on the NCRCities.com web site violates the NCRCities.com Terms of Use or any of NCRCities.com usage guidelines for specific products or services.

**Settings** :

You may choose to disable the cookie function through your browser. The website is viewable even if you disable the cookie function

You may choose not to provide certain personally identifiable information, but then you might not be able to participate in our surveys or contests or purchase NCRCities.com products.

**Security:**

NCRCities.com takes every precaution to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information to NCRCities.com, your information is protected both online and offline.

**Changes To Privacy Policy:**

NCRCities.com may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our web site.

If you have questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at info@ncrities.com
